{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Will Jenifer come to the party? I ______.",
      "a": "hope not",
      "b": "hope no",
      "c": "don't hope so",
      "d": "don't hope",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n\n- I hope not:  used to say that you hope something that has been mentioned does not happen or is not true\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Will you be on time? 'I ______?'",
      "a": "expect so",
      "b": "don't expect",
      "c": "so expect",
      "d": "I don't expect so",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- I expect so: spoken used to say that you expect something that has been mentioned happens or is true ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is it cold? \" Yes, I ______.\"",
      "a": "am afraid so",
      "b": "am afraid that yes",
      "c": "don't afraid so",
      "d": "don't afraid",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n\n- Hope/ think/ afraid/ say +so: used to refer back to an idea, action, quality, situation etc that has just been mentioned\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Will she come with us? 'I ______'",
      "a": "hope no",
      "b": "hope not",
      "c": "don't hope",
      "d": "don't hope so",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- I hope not: used to say that you hope something that has been mentioned does not happen or is not true ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Will they come in time? 'I ______'",
      "a": "expect so",
      "b": "don't expect so",
      "c": "expect no",
      "d": "expect that yes",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- I expect so: Â used to say that you expect something that has been mentioned happens or is true",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Children, _____ here!",
      "a": "you come",
      "b": "come",
      "c": "comes",
      "d": "to come",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is it going to be warm? 'I _____'",
      "a": "don't think so",
      "b": "think not",
      "c": "don't think",
      "d": "think no",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Hope/ think/ afraid/ say +so: used to refer back to an idea, action, quality, situation etc that has just been mentioned ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Children, ______ that!",
      "a": "don't make",
      "b": "don't do",
      "c": "don't you make",
      "d": "you don't do",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Will she finish in time? 'I ______'",
      "a": "expect so",
      "b": "expect yes",
      "c": "don't expect so",
      "d": "don't think",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- I expect so: used to say that you expect something that has been mentioned happens or is true ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Will you come with me? 'I am ______,'",
      "a": "afraid",
      "b": "afraid not",
      "c": "don't afraid",
      "d": "don't afraid so",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- I am afraid not: used to say that you are afraid something that has been mentioned does not happen or is not true ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}